

MYHAMMAD SHAHID

WEB DEVELOPER · MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+92 348 9176876





WORK EXPERIENCE

REACT JS DEVELOPER

Freelance Web Developer | Oct 2019 - present

- I have helped numerous businesses build their brand from design and prototype to a finished product.
- Leading a team of five mid-level designers
- Developed many Landing Pages, Blogs and Dashboards
- Provided support to clients
- Solved numerous front-end related issues.

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

Freelance App Developer | Aug 2021 - present

- Implemented overall Android and IOS application logic and wrote API server for Wi-Fi hotspot app. • Created numerous Micro Apps.

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Borcelle | Jul 2014 - Oct 2015

- Helping with day-to-day project tasks as well as monthly accountant tasks
- Editing photos for client projects
- Developing printed media ideas for restaurants

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

Keithston and Partners | 2013 - 2015

BA GRAPHIC DESIGN

Keithston and Partners | 2010 - 2013

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a senior graphic designer with 10 years experience in graphic design and UX design. I am also experienced in coordinating a team of mid-level designers.

EXPERTISE

UX Design
Graphics Design
Project Management
Branding

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Graphic Design Software
Software for Design
Another Software
Team Communication Sofware
Graphics Software

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creativity
Team building
Communication
Problem Solving
Leadership

thank you!

Q +92 348 9176876

(i) iShahidkahn

in iShahidkahn

Profile Summary

A freelance Web developer at Fiverr. 3+ years experience specializing in front-end development. A super nerd who loves Linux and enjoys customizing all of the development environments. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Professional Skill

- React JS, Redux
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Rest Api, Openai, PHP
- Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap 4/5
- Material UI
- MongoDB, MySQL

Relevant Skill

- Node IS
- Express JS
- Next IS
- Firebase
- DApp
- Ant Design

Education

University of Swat 2018-2022

B.S in Software Engineering

Work Experience

- I have helped numerous businesses build their brand from design and prototype or finished products.
- Created countless microSites.
- Developed many Landing Pages, Blogs, and Dashboards.
- Provided support to clients.
- Solved numerous front-end-related issues.

Projects

- Shopwithdice is a global directory of the best shops that can be found in each city, and their collections offer curations that source products
- directly from these stores.
- Bizroutes.com is a commercial route marketplace, where buyers can sell their routes and buyers can find routes for sale.

Interest

• Landing Pages

Dapp

Ai Projects

Shahid khan

Peshawar District, Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, Pakistan



shahidkhan123132@gmail.com



03489176876



linkedin.com/in/shahid-khan-1763711a1

Experience



f React Developer

Fiverr

Feb 2018 - Present (4 years 8 months +)

Hi, I am "Shahid Khan" a professional web developer and expert designer with a decade of successful freelancing experience now entering into a year of offering my services on this platform Having a solid customer review and reliable project completion portfolio I am the utmost suitable choice for your business.

local Software house

Local Corporation

Feb 2018 - Present (4 years 8 months +)

Education



University of Swat

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2018 - 2022

Skills

React.js • JavaScript • React Native • jQuery UI • Bootstrap